Carl Neuberg Papers ca.1880-1956 1940-1956 Mss.Ms.Coll.4
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1970-1975; 3 lin. feet
  - Immigranten Lied - Karl Farkes, n.d. (Box Series I: 6)
  - Indium Corporation of America, 1943 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Industrial and Engineering Chemistry, 1949 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Industrial Research Institute, Chattanooga Tenn., 1948-49 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Institute of Paper Chemistry, 1948 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Interchemical Corp., 1948-55 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Interscience Publishers, 1942-56 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Invertase Publishers, 1941-1942 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Ipatieff, Vladimir, 1947-40 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Isball, Horace S, 1942-48 (Box Series I: 6)
  - Jacobsohn, Kurt, 1929-56; 5 folders (Box Series I: 7)
  - Jacoby, Kurt, 1952-55 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Jacoby, Lotte, 1947 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Jacoby, Margarete, 1947-55 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Jahrstorfer, Michael, 1952-56 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Jander, G., 1952 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Java Pacific Line, 1940 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Jena Vertretung, n.d. (Box Series I: 7)
  - Jewish Cultural Reconstruction, Inc., 1951 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Jewish Way, 1943 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Johnson, Walter J., 1946-52 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Joslin, Elliot P, 1955 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Junk, W (publisher), 1945-56 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Just, G, 1916-17 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Jutrator, Jeanne(?), 1943 (Box Series I: 7)
  - von Kahler, Francis, 1947 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kaiser-Wilhelm Gesellschaft zur Forderung der Wisenschaften, 1925-49 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kaiser-Wilhelm Institut für Biochemie, 1927 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kaiser-Wilhelm Institut für Experimentelle Therapie, 1913 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kaiser-Wilhelm Institut für Physikalische Chemie und Elektrochemie, 1916 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kaiser-Wilhelm Institut für Zellphysiologie, 1952 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kalckar, Reman M, 1944-46 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kantrowitz, Dorothy, 1944 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kapfhammer, 1953 (Box Series I: 7)
  - S. Karger A.G., 1954 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Karpen, M, 1952-53 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kass, J. Peter, 1946-47 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kelemen, George, 1948 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Keller, 1942 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Keller, O., 1947 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Keller, Rudolf, 1943-54 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kelley, Vincent C., 1954 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Keto Chemical Co., 1942 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kimura, T., 1954 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kind, C. Albert, 1955-56 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kindler, Hilde, 1942 (Box Series I: 7)
  - King, Charles G., 1943 (Box Series I: 7)
  - King, Tsoo E., 1952 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kirk, Raymond E., 1949-52 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kisch, Bruno, 1946-56 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kisch, Guido, 1947 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kleeberg, L., 1955 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Klein, J. Raymond, 1943 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kleiner, Israel S, 1947-55 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Klema, Helene, 1954 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Klemperer, Paul, 1951 (Box Series I: 7)
  - von Klobusitzky, Dionysio, 1942-46 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Klopstock, Felix, 1947 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kluyver, Albert Jan, 1945-56 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Knoll, A.G., 1954 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kobel, Maria, 1948-56 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kodima, Kuzo, 1952 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kohn, Felix, 1952 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kohn, Moritz, 1952-54 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kolb, J. J., 1947 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kongelig Danske Videnskabernes Selskab, 1948 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Koopman, Louis, 1942 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Koppers Company, 1944 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kosak, A, 1954 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Koss, M., 1947 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kosterlitz, H., 1946 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kraut, Heinrich, 1955 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Krebs, H. A, 1954-55 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Krekeler, Heinz L., 1951-54 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kriegsministerium-Allgemeines Kriegs-Department, 1917-1918 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kriegchemikalien Aktiengesellschaft, 1916 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Krolof-Becker, Mignon, 1946-48 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kuhl, W. A., 1942 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kuhn, Richard, 1948 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kulka, Pauline, 1946 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kunitz, M, 1947 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kurono, K, 1956 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Kurz, S., 1912-48 (Box Series I: 7)
  - Lachs, Sophie, 1946 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lampen, J. O., 1952-53 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Landauer, Walter, 1944 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lane Wells Co., 1947 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lang, K., 1947 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lardy, Henry A., 1944-56 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lasch, Herbert, 1943 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Latzko, Ervin, 1952-55 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Laufer, Annie E, 1946-48 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Laufer, Stephen, 1942-49 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lautsch, W, 1952-54 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lederer, Marianne, 1943-56 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lederle Laboratories, 1943-49 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Ledingham, G. A., 1947 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lehr, David, 1956 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Leibowitz, J., 1955 (Box Series I: 8)
  - B.L. Lemke Company, 1943 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lemmerman, O., 1952 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lemoigne, M, 1948 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lendle, L, 1951-56 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lesser, Hilde, 1943 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Leseur, W. M., 1954 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Leszynski, W., 1947 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Levi, Leopold, 1947 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Levin, Louis, 1952 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Levine, Sumner, 1954 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Levy-Suhl, Max, 1946 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lewald, Theodor, 1947 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lewi, George, 1947-48 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Paul Lewis Laboratories, 1944-48 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Ley, Martha, 1954 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lichtenstein, Noah, 1947-55 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lieben, Fritz, 1943-53 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Liebig, 1880? (Box Series I: 8)
  - Liegner, Benno, 1949 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Eli Lilly and Company, 1945 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lindegren, Carl Clarence, 1952-56 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Linderstrøm-Lang, Kaj, 1954 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Linke, Agnes, 1947-53 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Linton, L. A., 1947 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lipikin, E, 1944 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lipmann, Fritz, 1944-56 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lipschitz, Werner, 1942-47 (Box Series I: 8)
  - von Loeti, Hartwig, 1947 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Loewenstein, Mara, 1946-54 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Loewi, Otto, 1951-56 (Box Series I: 8)
  - von Loon, Hendrik, 1943 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lowenstein, Marta, 1952 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Loy, Ernst, 1952 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lubrizol Corporation, 1954 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lucidol Corporation, 1942-43 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lüdtke, M., 1954 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lustig, Hilde, 1943-46 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lustig, Otto, 1943-53 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lynen, Fedor, 1951-55 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Lynen, Mrs. Fedor, 1954 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Maass, Berta, 1946 (Box Series I: 8)
  - McCollum, E. V., 1951-55 (Box Series I: 8)
  - McCouch, Grayson P., 1955 (Box Series I: 8)
  - McElroy, W. D., 1951 (Box Series I: 8)
  - McGonigal, Raoul, 1940 (Box Series I: 8)
  - A.D. Mackay, 1942-43 (Box Series I: 8)
  - McKenzie, Alex, 1943-47 (Box Series I: 8)
  - McLennan, 1952 (Box Series I: 8)
  - McRary, Willard L, 1952 (Box Series I: 8)
  - MacTavish, W. C., 1942-48 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Madison Foundation for Biochemical Research, 1947-54; 2 folders (Box Series I: 8)
  - Magnus-Levy, Adolf, 1942-48 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, 1946 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Mandl, Ines, 1953-56 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Mangold, Ernst, 1952-56 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Mannheimer, George, 1942 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Mannheimer, Hans S, 1943 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Manuscripts - Misc. (not Neuberg's) (Box Series I: 8)
  - Mark, Hermann, 1947-56; 2 folders (Box Series I: 8)
  - Markel, Louis, 1954 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Marquette University Library, 1942 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Martin, Gustav J., 1947 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Martin, Joseph J., 1955 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Marvel, C. S., 1948 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Marxov, Hedwig, n.d. (Box Series I: 8)
  - Masaryk, Jan, 1942 (Box Series I: 8)
  - S.E. Massengill Company, 1947 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Mastin, T. W., 1953 (Box Series I: 8)
  - Max-Planck-Gesellschaft zür Föderung der Wissenschaften, 1948-56; 3 folders (Box Series I: 9)
  - May, Albert Von, 1941-56; 2 folders (Box Series I: 9)
  - May, Elizabeth von, 1955 (Box Series I: 9)
  - May, U, 1942 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Mayer, Alfred, 1943 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Mayer, Claire (Mrs. Paul), 1942 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Mayer, Paul, 1942-43 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Mazia, Daniel, 1955-56 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Meirovsky, E., 1947 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Mellon Institute, 1942 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Menaker, Walter, 1952-53 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Menne, Fritz, 1953 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Merck & Co., 1942-51 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Mestern, Armand E, 1941-56 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Metal & Thermit Corp., 1948 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Methfessel, F., 1955 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Meyer, Fritz, 1942-48 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Meyer, J., 1947-54 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Meyer, Karl, 1948-54 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Meyer, Kurt H., 1947-51 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Meyer, L., 1947 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Meyer, R., 1949 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Meyerhof, Otto, 1947-49 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Michaelis, Leonor, 1947-50 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Michaelis, Moritz, 1954 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Micheel, Fritz, 1947-56 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Mietzsch, Fritz, 1952-53 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Mirsky, A. E., 1948 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Mittasch, Alvin, 1949 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Molinari, C, 1952 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Molinari, Irene, 1955 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Molitar, Haas, 1953 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company, 1942-48 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Montefiore Hospital for Chronic Diseases, 1944 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Mothes, K., 1954-56 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Mount Royal Hotel, 1942 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Münchner Chemische Gesellschaft, 1952 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Mulligan, R., 1947 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Muntz, John A., 1948 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Mutual of Omaha, 1955-56 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Myrbaek, Karl, 1947 (Box Series I: 9)
  - Müller-Zimmeman, 1933 (Box Series I: 9)
  - N-0, misc. (Box Series I: 10)
  - Nachmansohn, David, 1947-55 (Box Series I: 10)
  - Nagayana, T., 1952 (Box Series I: 10)
  - Nagelschmidt, Günther, 1952-56 (Box Series I: 10)
  - Nagelschmidt, Stepha, 1953 (Box Series I: 10)
  - Nathan, 1943 (Box Series I: 10)
  - Nathan, Blanche, 1942-47 (Box Series I: 10)
  - Nathan, Simon J., 1948 (Box Series I: 10)
  - National Aniline Division - Allied Chemical & Dye Corp., 1942 (Box Series I: 10)
  - National Brewers Academy, 1942 (Box Series I: 10)
  - National Geographic Society, 1946 (Box Series I: 10)
  - National Grain Yeast Corp., 1942-49 (Box Series I: 10)
  - National Sugar Refining Comp., 1944-52 (Box Series I: 10)
  - National Research Council, 1949-53 (Box Series I: 10)
  - National Vitamin Foundation, 1951 (Box Series I: 10)
  - National Yeast Products, 1954-56 (Box Series I: 10)
  - Neimann, W, 1947-48 (Box Series I: 10)
  - Nelson, J. M., 1946 (Box Series I: 10)
  - Neuberg, Carl (Box Series I: 10)
    - Addresses, Lectures - misc. (Box Series I: 10)
    - Addresses, Lectures - "Inorganic Oddities", n.d. (Box Series I: 10)
    - Awards & Diplomas, 4 folders (Box Series I: 10)
      See also oversize and extra-oversize folders
    - Awards & Diplomas (Box Series I: 10)
      - Budapesti Kir. Orvosegyesüllet, 1926 (Box Series I: 10)
      - Ceskoslovenska Akademie Zemedelska Praze, 1928 (Box Series I: 10)
      - Det. Kong. Danske Videnskabernes Selskab, 1929 (Box Series I: 10)
      - Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, 1956 (Box Series I: 10)
      - Regia Societas Scientiarum Upsaliensis, 1936 (Box Series I: 10)
    - Bibliography, 2 folders (Box Series I: 10)
    - Biographical Material (Box Series I: 10)
    - Biographical Material - newspaper clippings (Box Series I: 10)
    - Birthday Congratualtions, 1952; 7 folders (Box Series I: 11)
    - Birthday Congratulations, 1952 (Box Series I: 11)
      Société de Chimie Biologique Medal
    - Book Reviews, 1950-52 (Box Series I: 11)
    - Emil Starkenstein memorial (Box Series I: 11)
    - "Eroffnungsworte 1.x.1953, Homburg" (Box Series I: 11)
    - Manuscripts (Box Series I: 11)
      - "Die Aufloesung unloeslicher Materie in der Nature" (Box Series I: 11)
      - "Carbohydrates in yeast", 1942 (Box Series I: 11)
      - "Development of Chemistry Fermentation", ca.1942; 16p. (Box Series I: 11)
      - "Einfache Darstellung aktiver Zymaselösungen aus Bäckerhefe", ca.1953 (Box Series I: 11)
      - "Enzymatische Spaltung von Acetalen II", n.d. (Box Series I: 11)
      - "Herstellung von CaCo3", n.d. (Box Series I: 11)
      - "Jews in Biochemistry", 1947; 12p. (Box Series I: 11)
        Also includes biographical notes on Alfred Gottschalk (1p.), autobiographical notes on Neuberg (1p.), and 2 TLsS relating to publication of the article.
      - "Der Kreislauf des Phosphors", n.d.; 2 folders (Box Series I: 11)
      - "Nucleic acids, their derivatives and phosphatases" (Box Series I: 11)
      - "Physiologische Processe im Lichte stereochemischer Forschung", n.d. (Box Series I: 11)
      - "The Production of Glycerol from Sugar by Fermentation", n.d. (Box Series I: 11)
      - "Soluability of Insoluble Matter in Nature", n.d. (Box Series I: 11)
      - "Thionophosphatase", n.d. (Box Series I: 11)
      - "Transport of insoluable matter in nature", 1951 (Box Series I: 11)
      - "Über den Stand des Gärungsproblems" (Box Series I: 11)
      - "Zur Kenntnis der Glucuronsäure und über die Synthese gepaarter Glucuronsäuren", 1904 (Box Series I: 11)
      - "Improved methods for the determination of aldoses in the presence of ketoses", n.d.; 5p.; H. Lustig; Neuberg, Carl, b. 1877 (Box Series I: 11)
    - Manuscripts - misc., 2 folders (Box Series I: 11)
    - Medals, 3 folders (Box Series I: 11)
    - Military Records (see also Carl Neuberg - Personal Papers), 1917-35 (Box Series I: 11)
    - Notes, n.d.; 4 folders (Box Series I: 12)
    - Notes on Ribonsäure, n.d. (Box Series I: 12)
    - Patents (Box Series I: 12)
    - Personal, 1898-1956; 2 folders (Box Series I: 12)
    - Postal Service, 1947-52 (Box Series I: 12)
    - Radio Interview, 1947 (Box Series I: 12)
    - Reprints (Box Series I: 12)
      Removed from correspondence; see also separate reprint collection)
    - Unidentified and writings (Box Series I: 12)
  - Neuberg, Ernst, 1947-54 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Neuberg, Hans Werner, 1943-54 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Neuberg, Julius, 1946 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Carl Neuberg Society for International Relations: Neuberg medal, 1947-56; 2 folders (Box Series I: 12)
  - New York. Department of Health, 1947 (Box Series I: 12)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1946-47 (Box Series I: 12)
  - New York Academy of Sciences. Conferences on "Amino Acid Analysis of Proteins,", October 1945 (Box Series I: 12)
  - New York Medical College (Box Series I: 12)
  - New York Sugar Trade Laboratory, Inc., 1952-53 (Box Series I: 12)
  - New York University, 1942-55; 2 folders (Box Series I: 12)
  - New York University - invoices, 1943-44 (Box Series I: 12)
  - New York Universtiy Defense Committee, 1942 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Newton, A, 1955 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Niacet Chemicals Corporation, 1943-44 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Nichols, Joseph, 1953 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Nickerson, W. J., 1948 (Box Series I: 12)
  - van Niel, 1946 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Nilsson, Ragnar, 1947 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Nisizawa, Kazutosi, 1952-53 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Nissen, Rudolf, 1947 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Noack, Kurt, 1949 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Nomura, Masayasu, 1953 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Nord, (Frans) Friedrich, 1942-56 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Northrop, John H., 1947 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Northwestern Yeast Company, 1943 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Novelli, G. D., 1954 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Nozaki, Yasuhiko, 1954 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Nussbaum, Ilse, 1955 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Nutrition Foundation, 1943-49 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Oak Ridge Institute of Nuclear Studies, Inc., 1955 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1949-50 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Obervager, Charles A, 1942 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Ochiai, Eiji, 1952-54 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Ochoa, Severo, 1947-55 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Oestreicher, Elaa, 1954 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Olitzki, 1947 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Opitz, Kurt, 1951 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Oriental Yeast Industry Co., Ltd., 1951 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Orin, Zarick, 1946 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Osman, Elizabeth M, 1952 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Oster, Gerald, 1954 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Otto, Lisa G, 1953 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Overberger, Charles G, 1949-55 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Overman, Ralph T, 1951 (Box Series I: 12)
  - O.M.O.S. (Overseas Mail Order Service), 1949 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Ozark-Mahoning Co., 1948 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Paasen, Pierre von, 1942 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Pabst Brewing Co., 1949 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Pabst Laboratories, 1951 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Pace, D. M., 1947 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Pacsu, Eugene, 1947 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Panunzio, 1955 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Papdakis, Philippos E., 1946 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Parke Davis & Co., 1944-1947 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Partridge, Everett P., 1948 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Pasternak, Richard, 1942 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Pasternak, V. Z., 1952 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Patents (by others), 1905-1943 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Pehnack, Gertrud, 1947-1948 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Pelshenke, 1952 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Penick & Co., 1948 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Pennsylvania Salt Manufacturing, 1942-1943 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Pennsylvania Sugar Co., 1942 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Perlmann, Gertrude E., 1954 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Peter, Rudolph A., 1952 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Peterson, William Howard, 1942-1956 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Pfanstiel Chemical Co., 1943 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Pfizer & Co., 1942-1948 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Pflueger, Hildegard, 1955 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Philosophical Library, 1955 (Box Series I: 12)
  - Photographs (Box Series I: 13)
    - Neuberg, Carl (1), n.d.
    - Burk, Dean - Telsehow, Ernst - Warburg, Otto, n.d.
    - Burk, Dean - Warburg, Otto, n.d.
    - Burk, Dean, n.d.
    - Deuticke, Hans Joachim, n.d.
    - von Euler, Hans, n.d.
    - Fromageot, Claude, n.d.
    - Hahn, Otto - Telschow, Ernst, n.d.
    - Kaiser-Wilhelm-Institut (group photo with Neuberg), n.d.
    - Magnus-Levy, Adolf, n.d.
    - Mayer,Paul, n.d.
    - Nord, Friedrich Frans, n.d.
    - Ochoa, Severo, n.d.
    - Sobotka, Harry, n.d.
    - Thomas, Karl, n.d.
    - Warburg, Otto, n.d.
    - Wieland, Heinrich
    - Unidentified group photo (Neuberg in center, near front row), n.d.
  - Pick, Ernest P., 1916-1956 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Piel, Elmer, 1948 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Piel, Henry, 1942-1943 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Piel Brothers, 1942 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Pigman, Ward W., 1946-1951 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Pinkus, Felix, 1946-1947 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Pirie, N. W., 1948 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Pisha, B, 1953-54 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Plesch, Johannes, 1947 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Poggendorff-Redektion, 1955 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Pollak, W, 1956 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Poller, Harriet, 1943 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Pollock, Thomas C, 1948 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, 1951-54; 2 folders (Box Series I: 13)
  - Polytechnic Inst. of Brooklyn -Personnel, 1951-52 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Polytechnic Inst. of Brooklyn -Students, 1952 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Postal Telegraph-Cable Company, 1942-43 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Potter, Van R., 1943 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Poznanski, Andre M, 1949 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Poznanski, Leon and Ursula, 1947-52 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Prelog, V., 1947-48 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Price, Donald, 1944-47 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Proctor & Gamble Company, 1951 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Proskauer, Arthur, 1948 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Quaker Oats Company, 1942-46 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Quastel, Juda Hirsh, 1951-53 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Quimby, Oscar, 1947 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Rackner, E., 1947 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Rapp,., 1920 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Rare Chemicals, 1942 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Ratner, Sarah, 1949-54 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Rau, R. S. J., 1947-48 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Red Star Yeast and Products Co., 1953-56 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Reich, Gustave T., 1956 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Reichstein, T, 1946-49 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Reiff, Ferdinand, 1953 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Reilly Tar and Chemical Corp., 1944 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Reindel, F, 1952-55 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Reindel, Louise, 1952-54 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Reinold, Marianne, 1948-56 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Reiter, Melchior, 1951-55 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Reppe, Walter, 1952-55 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Reprints - others' (Box Series I: 13)
  - Research Council of Israel, 1953-54 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Resinous Products & Chemical Comp., 1945-46 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Reuter, Ernst, 1953 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Rewald, Walter, 1943 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Richard, Edgar, 1953 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Richtmyer, Nelson K., 1954 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Riebsomer, J., 1949 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Riesser, Hans E, 1954 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Riley, H, 1949 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Rinecker, A., 1952 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Rippel, August, 1955 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Ritchie, Patrick D., 1947-48 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Rittenberg, David, 1952-56 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Ritter, John J., 1943-46 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Roberts, Bruno R., 1942-56 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Roberts, Irene Neuberg (see also Forrest, Irene S.), 1943 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Roboz, Elizabeth, 1947 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1941 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research, 1948 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Roger, Robert, 1930 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Rohm & Haas Co., 1942-48 (Box Series I: 13)
  - Rollin, Paul T., 1942 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Roman, Wadim, 1946-56 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Ronwin, Edward, 1952-54 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Rose, William C, 1943-56 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Rosenfeld, Bruno, 1947 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Rosenow, George, 1954-55 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Rosenstiel, Edwin, 1947-48 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Rost, Eugen, 19 7 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Roth, Walter, 1946-47 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Rothenberg, Mortimer A., 1942-45 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Rothenberger, Emil M, 1947 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Rubensohn, Emmy Frank, 1946 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Rubin, Harvey N, 1952 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Rucker, 1952 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Sabalitschka, Theodor, 1947-52 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Sachs, Helena, 1943-56 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Sacks, Jacob, 1948 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Sadowsky, A, 1946-47 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Sakaguchi, Kin-ichiro, 1953 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Salem, H m, 1954-56 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Salinger, Lisa, 1942 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Salvesen, Robert, 1953 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Sanadi, D, 1954 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Sander, W, 1942 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Sankyo Company, Ltd., 1954 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Saphra, Ivan, 1946 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Sattler, Louis, 1946 (Box Series I: 14)
  - von Saucken, Hans, 1952 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Schaefer Brewing Co., 1942 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Scharefkin, D. M., 1946 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Scheminzky, F, 1951-53 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Schenley Distillers Corp., 1947 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Schenley Research Institute, 1943 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Scherbak, H., 1944 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Scherf, David, 1955-56 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Schindler, Kurt, 1952 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Carl Schleicher & Schuell Co., 1946 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Schlenk, 1955 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Schlenk, Fritz, 1941-54 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Schlenk, Wilhelm, 1952-56 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Schlesinger, Louis, 1943-48 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Schlitter, E, 1949 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Jos. Schlitz Brewing Co., 1946 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Schlubach, H. H., 1955 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Schmitt, L., 1952 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Schnellen, 1947 (Box Series I: 14)
  - Schnuchel, G., 1955 (Box Series I: 14)